PREVIOUSLY
-KARINA and WINTER of aespa!
-It's great to see you!
Yes, I plan to go very far today.
I hope our episodes are the funniest.
THAT'S AESPA'S SPIRIT
I can rotate my hand 360 degrees.
-What?
-What was that?
THE SEAL CLAP PARTY TRICK
WHY IS AESPA TRYING SO HARD?
We invited their right-hand men
and put together a new kind of team round.
Hello, I am head chef Kim Seon-yeop,
who's been working
with Chef Hyun-suk for 14 years.
I am Woo Do-hee,
and I work at L'Amant Secret.
What's one weakness that he has?
He tends to fish for praise.
He fishes for compliments.
I thought I'd end up
only cleaning up after him.
It's a rare sight to see him shy.
I got secondhand embarrassment
watching him.
Yes, I'm sure.
I'm looking forward to today.
AND
For the first time in the show's history,
they'll play with their right-hand men.
It's exhilarating
when teamwork is perfect.
-It's in 30-second intervals.
-Thirty seconds?
-Grind the black pepper.
-Yes, Chef.
-Did you add lemon juice?
-I did.
LIKE THEIR ACTUAL KITCHEN
PERFECT DETAILS
The teamwork of 14 years.
Where's the sugar, Seon-yeop?
Seon-yeop, lemon juice.
Is he cleaning up after him?
-Salt!
-Whoa!
SALT CROSS
THE TEAMWORK THEY'VE BUILT
FOR THE PAST 14 YEARS
So you have to be this good
to be fine dining chefs.
WHAT DO THEY TASTE LIKE?
-It's good.
-It's so tough to choose.
-It's getting harder.
This is KARINA's choice.
WHAT'S THE RESULT
OF THE FIRST ASSISTED TEAM ROUND?
You're watching Chef & My Fridge
with KARINA and WINTER of aespa.
Actually, we owe
a portion of our show to aespa.
-Have you watched us?
-So often.
-It's often trending on Reels.
-Is that so?
-He uses our songs the most often.
-Right.
You're facing this way today.
-I want to see them.
-It's as if we're facing each other.
He won't look at me.
ALL I NEED IS AESPA
All right.
-Some even say that…
-He's so silly.
…Ho-young has done the dance
more often than aespa themselves.
Even at the ceremonial first pitch.
Yes, I did the dance first
before pitching.
You did "su-su-su-supernova"?
Even at overseas events,
they'd have "Supernova" ready to play.
MUST DANCE EVEN WHEN ABROAD
They ask me to do the dance
before I actually get to work.
KARINA said,
as she watched him dance,
she felt a sense of familiarity
and sympathized with him.
Did you say this?
-Familiar?
-She felt he was familiar?
-With Ho-young.
-Me?
KARINA felt she was similar to him.
My arms are on the shorter end…
-Yes.
-…compared to my height.
-Really?
-I keep them folded, so not many know,
but they're short compared to my height,
and so, I'm good at recognizing
someone with short arms.
KARINA SYMPATHIZED WITH HIM
They are short.
-You probably notice them more often.
-They are short.
I don't think his arms are short.
I think his torso ate into his arms.
As he got bigger.
Yes, his torso began to expand.
-It got hungry.
-It ate into the arms.
Were you always aware of that
since you were young?
I didn't know,
but until middle school,
I was nicknamed T-Rex.
-What?
THE SHORT-ARMED DINOSAUR…
The dinosaur with these arms?
-Karinasaur.
-I'd always go, "They aren't that short."
But one day, I compared my arms
with the shortest girl in my class,
-and my arms were shorter.
-What?
I'm 168 cm tall,
and she was in the 140 cm range.
In the 140 cm range?
When you spread out like this,
she'll have less space here.
-They aren't that short!
-They aren't that short.
I'm sorry.
ADDICTED TO THE SEAL CLAP
So there's something
-KARINA wants to say to Eun-yeong.
-To me?
EXCITED
She says,
"Don't be mean to Ho-young and Sung-jun."
-Right.
-Seriously.
-She's mean.
-He has short limbs.
-She says they have short limbs.
It's the word "limbs."
-Right.
-The word itself?
TRIGGERED
-It was triggering.
-It hurts.
SELF-REFLECTION
I'm sure you've made efforts
to overcome that characteristic.
-I cover them up.
-Covering them up.
LIKE THIS?
HAIR TOO SHORT
-Use your hair.
-To divert attention from my arms.
-That's why I'm quick with my steps.
-Yes.
We'd like to offer Ho-young
a special opportunity.
-Would you like to dance with her?
-Together?
Yes, with KARINA.
GETS UP IMMEDIATELY
KARINA X JUNG HO-YOUNG'S DANCE!
It's an honor.
THE HONOR IS MINE
-What now?
-Make sure you learn from her.
The ratio difference is uncanny.
THE DIFFERENCE IS SO EVIDENT…
THE SUPER UDON IS ON ITS WAY!
Ready, go.
Su-Su-Su-Super Udon
HER UPPER BODY MOVES WITH THE LEGS
ONLY MOVING THE UPPER BODY
She's moving the legs too.
-Move your legs.
-Your legs are still.
-He's…
-Whoa!
OOH, AHH
HIS TEACHER GIVES HIM A LESSON
HIS LEGS FINALLY BEGIN TO MOVE
-We only focused on the arms.
-We did!
AFTER THE LESSON, ONE MORE TIME
DIVERTING ATTENTION
FULLY CHARGED WITH CONFIDENCE
His dancing looks much better now.
-That was different.
-It was better.
-Now I know the real dance.
-Yes.
It's much better
now that our attention is diverted.
A TIP FOR THE SHORT-ARMED
-The key was moving the legs.
-It was much better with the legs.
All right.
We received a tip.
As of this taping,
KARINA is about to challenge herself
to something big tomorrow.
It's literally her D-day.
-Yes, it's important.
-What's this about?
Tomorrow, I have
my driver's license test.
Driver's license test?
Tomorrow is the test?
-The on-road driving exam.
-The on-road? She must be nervous.
-You did the course?
-The driving course test
ended with full marks.
I KNEW IT
Are you licensed to drive?
This is the first time I'm sharing this,
but yes, I am.
-Whoa.
-Really?
-You passed.
-I did.
Let's cheer for KARINA
so that she'll pass with one try.
OH MY
WE HOPE YOU PASS THE DRIVING TEST
You might as well
show up in person to show support.
I'm about to show up at the office.
You can go, "KARINA! You got this!"
-Huh? What's this?
-Hey, wait.
Unlike us, there's someone
who's against you getting
-your driver's license?
-Someone's against this?
-So your father is adamantly against this?
-Your father?
I don't want to sound like
I'm trying to make my dad sound great,
but he said, "It's my joy
to pick you up when you call."
THE DAD WITH A DAUGHTER CAN RELATE
BLUSH
-He must love picking her up.
-He said I won't need it.
He's such a doting father,
and he always sends flower baskets
whenever I hold concerts
with the sweetest messages attached.
When I go on a tour,
he'd mark my whereabouts on the map.
MARKING HER WHEREABOUTS ON THE MAP
-That's why he's against it.
-He's very sweet.
You know, her sweet father
with all these stories
once served in the Marine Corps.
So within the Marine Corps,
aespa and KARINA were famous
even before they made their debut.
We have proof, so let's see it.
-Oh, please don't.
-Whoa. What is it?
There it is.
It's the Marine Corps
social media account.
FAINTS
-"Yu Cheol's daughter is"…
-His daughter.
-…"debuting as a girl group."
-Yu Cheol's daughter.
"We're proud of her
overcoming many days as a trainee."
"Yu Ji-min was a member of aespa,
debuting as KARINA."
-It drives me nuts.
-She was posted
on the Marine Corps social media account.
-Is that the official account?
-It's the official one.
It's the official account.
-You're big among the Marines.
-Yes.
I'm huge.
BLUSH
It feels really weird
to see my dad's name here.
-Yu Cheol's daughter.
Yu Cheol.
She's a beloved daughter
with a doting father at home,
but she's also aespa's leader.
Has your personality changed
during your career?
I'm the youngest at home,
so I used to be the cutesy type.
But our members are all avoidant types.
The other three?
Including me.
All four of you?
When we have to make a decision,
we always go, "She'll do it."
So you put it on each other.
So I have to go,
"Is it yes or no? Tell me,
or we're not going home."
THE LEADER HAS BECOME RESOLUTE
-Has your personality changed over time?
-It definitely did.
Speaking of, let's ask Chef Seon-yeop
what Hyun-suk is like as a leader.
Yes, his own leader.
CURIOUS
-He's a type who sets an example.
-He sets an example?
How does he set an example?
The motto of our restaurant
is to let our customers leave
with the feeling that
they have watched a fun comedy film.
That's our motto.
When he walks out,
-he asks me to get him some salt.
-Right.
-He asks for some salt in his hand…
-…to do a tour around the tables.
-A round.
Does he go around with salt in his hand?
I have to give it to him in a small dish.
So he's pretty much
the restaurant's clown!
"Let the clown in!"
And he comes in with salt, "Yessir!"
YOU LITTLE…
It's like hand-pulled noodles.
-You're right.
-Like at those hot pot places.
-He's performing like the noodle guy.
-A performance.
CHEF & MY FRIDGE HAS HYUN-SUK'S SALT
I actually like my food bland
but you can make mine salty.
GOTCHA
GIGGLING
GOT MY RESPECT…
It'll be drenched in salt.
Chef Jong-won, what kind of leader
do you think you are?
There are many younger people in my team,
so I try not to be stuck up.
I believe
I'm not the stuck-up kind of leader.
I try to understand their language too,
like abbreviations.
Like yareu?
-The dishes today are yareu.
-It's so yareu.
She hates that slang.
You don't like yareu?
What does it mean?
-When people feel great. Yareu.
-Yareu.
-Geez.
-Back in my day, it was "Oh, yareu."
Why do you hate it?
It's just the word itself, it's…
-Sounds shallow?
-Yes!
Hey, KARINA. Yareu.
SHUDDERING
WINTER, yareu.
GIGGLING
aespa is here today, yareu!
So you don't like that?
-Yareu.
He's definitely not the stuck-up type.
-But does he think so?
-Right?
We have a transcript.
-A transcript?
-I knew this would come up.
I knew it.
Do-hee talked about team dinners,
-and he seems to have a different opinion.
-What did he say?
"There's too much pressure
on our team dinners."
What's the reason?
EYES WIDENED
-But he's so nice to you.
-I knew this was the case.
-Do you force him to drink?
-It's never forced.
-Then why is there so much pressure?
-Right?
He never forces us
to come to team dinners,
but it's because he's always serious
whenever he does something.
For example, when we go bowling,
-there's pressure when I'm on his team.
-I get it.
Does he have to win?
He has to win.
EVERYONE SIGHS
Team dinners are supposed to be fun.
I wouldn't go.
JUST FINDS IT HILARIOUS
Chef Do-hee also shared with us
that even for team dinners,
Jong-won has to plan everything out.
Are you serious?
-How tiring.
-In five-minute intervals?
It's to produce some fun.
-Because it has to be fun.
-He just mentioned one of them.
What about a toast? Do you make those?
We do that too.
I heard you have to make
an acrostic poem with his name.
He has to make an acrostic poem
with Jong-won's name for the toast?
-I've seen it.
-With your name?
Do you have to do
card stunt performances too?
-With cards.
-Yes, with colored cards.
-Son! Jong! Won!
-Jong! Won!
-The best!
SON JONG-WON, KNOCKED OUT
-Right?
-I guess he does that.
Even for team dinners,
I want to do something
that isn't too cliché,
so I try my best to let them have fun.
I didn't know he took it like this.
JOKING
-He wanted to make it different.
-Yes.
It's completely different from ours.
-What do you do?
-For us… He should be talking, actually.
-Tell us.
-I just pay the tab
and give them my credit card
to go karaoke or something.
I do that to let them relax and have fun.
It must've taken lots of self-control
for him not to go karaokeing.
How bad would he have wanted to go!
It's incredible. Give him a hand!
YOU'RE INCREDIBLE, CHOI HYUN-SUK
This guy who loves to sing
doesn't follow them to the karaoke room?
FEELING PROUD
And now, following WINTER's fridge
in the previous episode,
we're about to look
through KARINA's fridge.
Feel free to use
the shelf-stable ingredients.
And let me make a note
that these bottles here are KARINA's.
Do you have more alcohol inside?
-They're only out here.
-Only out here?
Quite the true drinker.
Those who do not drink their alcohol cold
-are truly those who love to drink.
-Is that so?
WINTER has a long way to go.
She specializes
in drinking from the bottle.
STRAIGHT FROM THE BOTTLE
SHE'S DEFINITELY NUMBER 1 IN THAT AREA…
EMBARRASSED
-Let's take a look at her fridge.
-Okay.
-I'm nervous.
-Let's look through her fridge.
We present KARINA's fridge!
AMAZED
PRESENTING KARINA'S FRIDGE
There are lots, right?
-Even WINTER looks surprised.
-That's a lot.
What's that?
It's yareu.
Ugh!
Look at the top two shelves.
The first and the second shelves
-have so many side dishes.
-That's a lot.
Who made all these for you?
They're all from my aunt,
my mom's older sister.
My mom is currently abroad
to study another language.
AMAZED
So my aunt made those side dishes
instead of my mom.
You must be so grateful.
-Do you prefer Korean food?
-Absolutely.
She says she loves Korean food.
-It's a lot, right?
-These are all Korean side dishes.
I probably have lots of kimchi.
-You do.
-She does have a lot.
The second shelf is all kimchi.
It's almost like a kimchi fridge.
ALMOST LIKE A KIMCHI FRIDGE
-You've already had a lot.
-Yes, she has already had some.
-Yes.
-She had lots. Look at how empty it is.
Look. It does look delicious.
-It's really good.
-Is it kkakdugi?
-Young radish kimchi.
-It already looks great.
-Perfect with ramyeon.
-It's so good.
You can already tell right here
that she's a Korean food person.
But why is she named KARINA?
HIS REMARK WAS SO YAREU
She's KARINA
because she likes beer with her kimchi.
-Whoa.
-KARINA, bring some Corona.
OH…
EVEN THE GRANDPA'S MAD
That was so corny.
HIS COMMENT WAS SO CORNY
You don't dislike Western food, right?
No, but I can't make anything,
so I usually go out
to eat Western cuisine.
POTATO, SPINACH, CELERY, ZUCCHINI…
We're going to see lots of stuff.
She has some fruit
on the third shelf, including watermelon.
-What are these? Kiwis?
-Kiwis.
-It's a lot.
-They aren't ordinary kiwis,
but ruby kiwis.
-What now?
-Ruby kiwis.
-It's red inside, right?
-Yes.
When it's cut in half,
it's ruby-red on the inside.
And it's much sweeter.
SOUNDS DELICIOUS
I'm allergic to kiwis,
but I still eat them.
-Because it's good?
-Allergic?
-You just eat it?
-You put up with it?
-Yes, I just scratch myself later.
-Scratch yourself?
-Try some. It's really good.
-It's really good.
-It's really good?
-It is.
CHOP
-So there's the color.
-Isn't it pretty?
IT'S REALLY RUBY-RED
You can get it out like this.
POPS OUT
YUM
He ate the sticker.
HE EVEN ATE THE STICKER
PTOOEY…
-It's good.
-Yes, it's good.
PROUD
KARINA, I hear you're the type
who puts on weight quickly
and sheds it quickly too.
My weight fluctuates a lot.
-I've gained 4 kg in one day…
-In a day?
-…and I've shed it on the same day.
-Did she say 4 kg?
Is that possible?
But how?
It was back when I was a trainee.
That day, I stuffed myself
with everything I wanted,
felt so full, and tapped on my belly.
I knew it was trouble, so I weighed myself
and saw I had gained 4 kg.
IN TOTAL SHOCK
The next day was our weigh-in day,
so I turned up the heater
in the practice room,
put on leggings, a sweat suit,
a zip-up hoodie on top
and a padded jacket.
A padded jacket?
Yes, and we played the top 100 chart
and ran around together.
After that, I went home
and did an hour of lower-body bathing.
When I did that,
I was completely drenched in sweat.
-You dried yourself out.
-I did.
I hear UFC fighters do that.
And you dropped 4 kg?
But now,
I'm too old
to eat or work out like that.
-Because she's too old?
-Do you feel
that you've become a bit older?
Recently, very much.
I'm in pain when it rains.
LOL
She's in pain when it rains?
-Yes, it aches when it rains.
-Because you're older?
We have a guy who went through the famine.
THE GRANDPA
IS SERIOUSLY IN PAIN IN THE RAIN
He's even used a pack carrier.
A pack carrier?
I guess people don't use those anymore.
Let's look at the freezer.
Frozen cocktail shrimp.
Mackerel.
-What's in here? Meat.
-Meat.
-I probably have a lot.
-Yes, meat.
Yes, and you have many different cuts.
You have lots of meat.
I really love meat.
What if you can only have
one cut of meat right now?
THAT'S SO HARD TO CHOOSE…
Can't she just have a whole pig?
MAKE IT EASIER
ONE WHOLE PIG
-My all-time favorite is pork belly.
-Pork belly.
I love it.
I can have it all week long
and not get sick of it.
She could've been nicknamed T-Rex
because she likes meat so much.
-A carnivore?
-Yes, because it's a carnivore.
She loves meat a lot.
That's all for KARINA's fridge!
FINISHED CHECKING OUT KARINA'S FRIDGE
What kind of orders
does she have today for the chefs?
Show us her orders!
What does she want to order?
I Woke Up
and Found Myself in Cooking Comics.
-That sounds hard.
-Right.
What do you mean by this?
-I love to read comics…
-Right.
…so I want to eat something that's good
but also looks like
something from a comic book.
-Special.
-Something special.
I wanted to put that order in
because I wanted to get
a dish that makes me feel like
I'm reading a comic book.
So it needs to look creative.
-Yes, I hope so.
-This one
-is advantageous for Poong.
-You're right.
THAT'S TRUE
You should join the round.
-Think about it.
-We'll see.
-After seeing the second one.
-Let me see it.
-I don't think Hyun-suk will pick it.
-Right.
When he wakes up,
he's like, "I'm glad I'm still alive."
What are you trying to say?
When he wakes up, he goes, "I'm alive."
You aren't much younger than I am.
ALSO IN HIS 50S, BUT DRAWS THE LINE
-"I'm alive today."
-"I'm still alive."
All right.
Now, what's the second order
KARINA has brought?
-Lemonade.
-That one
-is a part of your lyrics.
-Yes.
It's actually "I'll make it LEMONADE."
So please make me lemonade
and a dish
that'll go well with the beverage.
I thought I'd ask.
Food pairing.
-She used a part of the lyrics.
-That's right.
The fight has already been set,
because these two
will have to play as teams.
Chef Hyun-suk and Jong-won
must join the same round.
Yes, join the same round.
Also, the same applies
to Poong and Chef Eun-yeong.
All you have to do is pick the order.
Which order will you take?
Poong just raised his hand.
I'll go to the place where I belong.
I'll take the cooking comics round.
Naturally, I'll go with him.
You're his natural enemy.
She has never lost once against Poong.
She's that good.
Now, Poong and Eun-yeong are set.
Naturally, the team round is also set,
a dish that'll go well with lemonade.
Chef Seon-yeop, are you pleased with this?
Will he make less of a mess
for you to clean up?
I'll have to keep an eye on him.
YOU TOO, SEON-YEOP?
Do you like this order, Jong-won?
Two people don't necessarily mean
it's twice as efficient.
It can go up by three to four times,
so we'll do a good job together.
WE'LL SHOW YOU A GREAT ROUND
I'll truly do my best.
WITH ALL OF HIS HEART!
BEFORE THE HISTORICAL TEAM ROUND…
Then let us begin the round between
Webtoon Artist Poong and Chef Eun-yeong!
THE COOK-OFF BEGINS NOW
This is the first cook-off
using KARINA's ingredients.
A woman who woke up
and found herself in comedy comics,
Chef Park Eun-yeong,
versus a man who woke up
and found himself in bizarre comics,
Webtoon Artist Kim Poong.
I have a feeling
that Poong has an advantage.
-Probably.
-After all, he's a webtoon artist.
He used to draw.
-Currently a chef.
-A TV personality who was an artist.
When it comes to this, "I Woke Up
and Found Myself in Cooking Comics,"
Poong has already made a few masterpieces.
The infamous dung loach
has become his biggest work so far.
In the past,
-he has made the larva rice.
-The larva.
They're like larvae on leaves!
HAHAHAHAHAHA
THIS WAS ALSO FOR THE ORDER,
"A DISH OUT OF A COMIC BOOK"
-We call it a piece of work.
-Of course.
-The larva rice.
-Is it really?
Are you sure you'll be fine
with a bizarre looking dish?
Actually, something like dung loach
was what I wanted to see today.
Please make me a masterpiece.
-I'm glad you're here.
-Wait.
OH…
We just got quite a scandalous transcript.
-What is it?
-It's from Eun-yeong.
"I, Park Eun-yeong,
am the KARINA of Chinese cuisine."
You said this?
-What?
-When did you say this?
-Says who?
I AM KARINA, I CAN'T BE TWO
I didn't say that.
That was a prevalent notion
in the world of Chinese cuisine.
I didn't say it myself.
-Who said that?
-I've never heard it.
Poong, you've set a foot
into the world of Chinese cuisine,
so have you heard this?
I've never heard it in my life.
That's why I say you are
a bootleg Chinese chef from the streets.
This kind of hearsay
does not reach the streets.
Only those who are
authentically in the field have heard it.
You'll get lots of awful DMs today.
So non-Chinese chefs can't hear it?
Then let's ask Witch With a Wok,
who's in the field. Have you heard it?
-I've heard it.
-Really?
-So Eun-yeong is the KARINA in her field?
-So authentic chefs have heard it.
-Yes, only us.
-Why?
-What?
-I've heard this too.
-You have?
-But I think she misheard it.
Someone who was walking by
wanted a bottle of beer from her,
so they said,
"Do you have a bottle of Corona?"
-Corona?
-No, it's not like that.
-I think you misheard it.
-Listen to this guy.
He's getting ambitious.
Not Corona, but KARINA, right?
Yes, you're right. It's not Corona.
KARINA of Chinese cuisine.
Again, whoever wins the cook-off
will get the Chef & My Fridge tableware
as a prize.
I want it too.
I have to get it.
CHEF EUN-YEONG'S INGREDIENTS:
PORK BELLY, PORK SHOULDER,
POTATO, RADISH, JJAJANG RAMYEON SOUP BASE
What are you making, Chef Eun-yeong?
I'm making ArmagePork
with her favorite ingredient,
pork belly.
It's a jjajang fried rice dish.
-My gosh.
-I'll make jjajang fried rice
and stack it up like a tree
as if it's from a comic book.
-As you all know…
-Jjajang tree?
…KARINA is famous
as the icy-looking AI-like beauty,
but I believe she's very warm-hearted.
So on the outside,
it'll look like a pretty tree,
but once you cut it in half,
you'll see the dark rice inside.
I wanted to express
the beautiful twist that KARINA has.
It sounds like a dish from comics.
Different inside and out.
KIM POONG'S INGREDIENTS: PORK NECK,
SHRIMP, BEECH MUSHROOM, SWEET PUMPKIN
SPINACH, KIMCHI, RICE PAPER,
BALSAMIC SAUCE, OYSTER SAUCE
Up against Eun-yeong is Poong.
What are you making?
The name of my dish is
Karinasaur.
Are you talking about her nickname?
I'll make a Karinasaur,
which will look like
it came right out of a comic book.
Like a Pikachu cutlet?
Is he making me a dinosaur?
So how will you make that dish?
Well… I'll make it edible, so don't worry.
-Don't worry about it.
-No words needed.
DID I JUST HEAR THAT RIGHT?
You said you wanted it to be funny
and somehow edible, right?
THIS IS SO SCARY…
So don't worry about anything
and just put your focus on how it looks.
-We'll see when it's ready.
-Sure.
This time, WINTER will join me
for the five-minute check.
All right.
And now,
let us begin the round, "I Woke Up
and Found Myself in Cooking Comics."
"My twin sister was actually KARINA."
Self-claimed KARINA of Chinese cuisine,
Chef Park Eun-yeong.
I can't believe this nonsense.
-You can't believe it?
-Seriously.
Here to send KARINA to Jurassic Park,
The Steven Poongpielberg of the show,
Webtoon Artist Kim Poong.
Will they capture KARINA's heart
with dishes right out of a comic book?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
It's all about the visuals.
INTO THE WORLD OF COMICS!
Can you peel this?
But just the green part.
-He gives him a job so smoothly.
-Seriously.
-Are you acting as his kitchen toolman?
-Sure.
-You have to peel that?
-Yes.
He needs just the green part.
It needs to look so good
that it captures our viewers too.
ONION
What's he going to make?
How's he going to make a dinosaur?
I don't have enough time.
Chili peppers, garlic, onion, and pork.
Pork and shrimp. He'll grind everything.
SOY SAUCE, OYSTER SAUCE, COOKING WINE
-Didn't you put in too much?
-Isn't it way too full?
What's he trying to do?
-It's not working. It's an emergency.
-It won't even close.
-He's nervous.
-It closed.
-Oh, no.
-Will it work?
-It's working.
-It's grinding.
Karinasaur.
Okay.
Just a little bit of red pepper powder.
The ground ingredients.
-The dinosaur skin?
-The skin?
That's so scary.
-It's scary.
-What's that?
-It's the filling, like dumpling fillings.
-Dumplings.
KARINA, between the taste
and how it looks,
if one looks very shocking
but isn't as good, would you pick that?
If it's overwhelmingly shocking, I would.
She's putting lots of focus
on how the dish looks.
The visuals.
This time, how it looks
is as important as how it tastes.
-Potato.
It's jjajang, so it needs that.
Why does she need so much?
Will she cook it in the microwave?
I'm sure most people have seen
what jjajang fried rice looks like.
But she mentioned a tree,
so we're looking forward to that.
What's she trying to do?
It's hard to imagine.
NEXT, RADISH SLICES
She's making thin radish slices.
-Radish?
-Radish and jjajang rice?
-You're right.
-Will that become the tree?
-How will she make a tree?
-Radish pickles?
Maybe she'll cover the outside
with those slices.
Sung-jun, can you cut these out
with those cookie cutters?
-More bigger pieces than small ones.
-Yes, ma'am.
Wait, she's older?
GETTING CHILLS
Much older.
-You're all making others do lots of work.
-They don't even hesitate.
-Sung-jun and Sam are helping.
-I want to see her cook, though.
And some green onion.
CHOP CHOP CHOP CHOP!
You'll hurt your hand! Slow down!
NOT AS PRECISE AS THE SOUND…
He'll make a dinosaur shape
-and fill it with that.
-The filling.
-I wonder how he'll make the dinosaur.
-Right?
It's probably like a dim sum.
T-Rex dim sum.
ONE AT A TIME
Sung-jun, you need to hurry. I need lots.
Wait.
It's an emergency.
LEARNED THE "WAIT" MOVE FROM HIS MASTER
Cut many pieces at once.
Wait.
HIS STUDENT ONLY LEARNS THE BAD THINGS…
Do you need more? Look.
-That should be enough.
-Okay.
Okay. That's enough.
Doesn't that look like dinosaur skin?
Right?
All right, today… This goes in.
Okay.
What's that? Pumpkin peels?
-The peels?
-He's boiling the peels.
It's too tough to eat,
so it's usually thrown out.
2. BOIL SWEET PUMPKIN PEELS
AND SPINACH IN SALTED WATER
I'm seeing lots of green stuff.
-It must be for the color.
-You're right.
-Will that become the skin?
-Like scales?
It's green like T-Rex.
MY SKIN
-Whoa.
-I guess so.
What's that? Spinach?
Sung-jun, there's no time to watch him.
Chop-chop.
HARD ON HER YOUNGER FRIEND
-Wait.
-Make as many as possible.
-This is too much.
-What?
Stack a few slices and do it at once.
-I can do it with many slices.
-Hey.
I need lots.
You were doing it a slice at a time?
Cut out a few slices at once.
-Whoa. Awesome.
-It works, right?
You have less than ten minutes.
SURPRISED
Time really flies.
-Time is passing by so quickly.
-Yes, what's going on?
-It's because we're watching them.
-Nothing's ready.
QUICKLY CHOPS ONION
WHAT ABOUT PORK BELLY?
I get that Chef Eun-yeong
is making jjajang fried rice.
ONION, INSTANT RICE,
JJAJANG RAMYEON SOUP BASE
Eun-yeong is very nimble.
Jjajang rice.
Did you cook that?
TELEPATHY
DOESN'T IT LOOK GOOD?
It looks good.
Eight minutes and forty seconds left.
Where did the time go?
Chinese chefs are very fast.
But Poong does need to win
at least once against her.
He's very busy right now.
He's so busy.
Can you check and see if it's burning?
SIZZLING
I think it'll burn soon.
-Hey, it's burning. Hurry.
-It's burning?
FLOUNDERING!
CHUCKLE…
-Lower the heat.
-No, it's okay.
I have to keep cooking it.
RUNNING BACK TO THE BLENDER!
Rice paper?
He's turning rice paper into powder.
Are those for the scales?
It's so hard to tell.
He looks so busy.
-Are you going to blend that?
-Yes.
He's blending lots of stuff.
It's still hard to tell what he's making.
-What's that?
-Is that kimchi juice?
-It's kimchi juice.
-He added kimchi juice.
I have no idea what he'll make.
I think he's focusing on the color
and completely disregarding the taste.
Is it just for the color?
I guess that's not for her to eat.
LOL
Hey, can you do this for me?
-How many times has he used the blender?
-Right?
It's the most times for anyone ever.
He just added
ground rice paper into the mix.
WHAT IS HE MAKING, REALLY?
The paper will add that chewy texture.
RIGHT!
Maybe it'll turn into dough.
WILL HE MAKE DOUGH WITH THAT?
No way.
Now that he's focused on cooking,
he's really boring.
THE FUNNESS CRITIC IS BACK
He used to be funny
when the order was about comics.
I don't care about being funny.
I'm not even sure if I'll finish.
Something's on his hair.
He got kimchi juice on his hair.
HOW DID THAT END UP THERE?
That's a cut from a comic book.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT
Seven minutes remain.
-You're over halfway through.
-Time flies.
Time really does fly.
-Done.
-Okay.
-We're done, Eun-yeong.
-You are?
-We should see a tree soon, Eun-yeong.
-Right?
She strains the radish slices.
And she's now seasoning them.
-She's pickling them.
-Pickling?
Is that the side dish?
No idea what they're doing.
We're not seeing anything yet.
-Is that the dough?
-He's blending something again.
-He's on it now.
-You're making the dough now?
3. MIX FLOUR WITH PUMPKIN-SPINACH JUICE
TO MAKE GREEN DOUGH
Poong isn't saying anything today.
FULLY FOCUSED WITH KIMCHI IN HIS HAIR
More.
He has never won against Eun-yeong,
-so he has to win today.
-Please!
Will it be done in time?
He'll probably make
the dinosaur skin with that dough.
-Six minutes.
-Six?
-Six minutes. It's an emergency!
-Six minutes left.
Where did the time go?
The green dough looks very nice.
-Poong's dough?
-Yes, it looks good.
-It looks nice.
-He made dough?
-What will he do with it?
-It'll have to cook, right?
-I'm not sure if it'll be edible.
-I don't know if it'll be cooked.
-I'm not so sure.
-What's he doing?
Can I get my driver's license tomorrow?
CAN I WAKE UP SOUND AND SAFE?
Ugh!
It can't just look good.
It has to be edible too.
-Okay.
-It has to be edible.
Yes, forget the taste for now.
-Dang it.
-All right.
Why did I join the comics round?
BELATED REGRETS
He's preparing
the biggest masterpiece of his life.
The biggest masterpiece of his life?
You got this.
I'm not seeing anything yet.
She'll make a tree with potatoes.
They aren't cooked.
-Eun-yeong mashes the potatoes.
-They aren't cooked yet.
-The potatoes aren't cooked?
-They aren't.
-Did you pull them out too quickly?
-Microwave them again.
-They're raw.
-Should I?
Sung-ju, five minutes left!
Please report from the kitchen.
-Yes, WINTER!
-WINTER.
Go on now.
We're on our way to the kitchen.
Gosh. The glass bowl.
EUN-YEONG STEAMS THE POTATOES AGAIN!
Nothing's ready. There's nothing to taste.
Five minutes already? Oh, my gosh.
-Do you want me to do it?
-Wait.
-Okay.
-We're on our way to the kitchen.
I'm here with WINTER.
-Can we try this?
-What?
We'll try this one.
SKETCHING
Okay.
-WINTER and I will…
-Hurry.
BOO…
MY SAMPLE…
WINTER, you can try this.
She's giving it a taste.
I'm dying to know.
-She knows what KARINA likes.
-What is it?
It must be good.
WHAT IS IT?
It's totally T-Rex.
-It's totally T-Rex?
-Really?
Gosh. Phew.
-KARINA would love this.
-Really?
-Totally T-Rex?
What does that mean?
-T-Rex flavor?
-It's like spicy fried rice.
Spicy fried rice?
It's delicious. Not bad.
-Just make the shape convincing.
-Yes.
4. PUT THE FILLING ON THE DOUGH
AND COVER IT WITH DOUGH
Okay. Okay, okay.
It's like a dinosaur dumpling.
Yes, a dinosaur dumpling.
STARTING TO GET INTERESTING
-You have 3 minutes and 44 seconds.
-That's hot.
Now, 3 minutes and 44 seconds. It's hot?
-Eun-yeong grabs the fried rice.
-She's piling it up.
-Can you taste the jjajang rice?
-Jjajang rice.
WINTER, try the jjajang rice.
Does it make you sing "Armageddon"?
What's it like?
It's totally jjajang rice.
-It's just jjajang rice?
-It's ordinary jjajang rice?
She doesn't lie.
It's just jjajang rice.
Eun-yeong begins to make the shape!
She's shaping the rice.
So that's the tree.
WHAT'S KIM POONG UP TO?
He'll cut it with scissors now.
The head. He's making the head.
SLICE
-Karinasaur.
-We have to see the dinosaur soon.
-Is that the face?
-How is that…
-That's not going to be done.
-He's grilling it.
-It'll turn too hard.
Is that the arm?
It looks like a map of Korea.
I think that's the head and the tail.
He'll probably add
the arms and legs later.
But if the dough does not cook fully,
I think it will be funny.
-But it has to be done.
-What about me?
-You won't be able to drive tomorrow.
-It has to look good and be cooked.
I get why he's taking time off
from making webtoons.
-Poong, yes.
-It's done.
It looks like the alphabet F.
-He'll fry it.
-The oil.
That'll turn into a dinosaur.
-Be careful.
POURING
He's deep-frying it now.
-Look at his face.
-He's cooking it right now.
-Yes.
-He's cooking it like this.
-It's like that.
-It's a dinosaur with an open mouth.
-A dinosaur with an open mouth?
-It's the profile, just the head.
You know what?
He's still working on another part.
-He's making short arms.
-A minute and 40 seconds.
DROP
You can't give KARINA a stomachache.
-He's making these.
-You can't give KARINA a stomachache.
-It won't stick like that.
-Stick it on first before frying.
THE ARM SLOWLY RISES…
Why won't these cook all the way?
THIS PERSON IS GROWING ANXIOUS…
-Right.
-But you don't have enough time.
-They aren't fully cooked.
-Eun-yeong.
-Blend the potatoes for her.
-Potatoes?
WHACK!
-Why won't these get cooked?
-Oh, no.
-Hey.
-How can I mash undercooked potatoes?
But I put them in for seven minutes.
I have to turn them into dough.
No, there's nothing.
Just blend them.
The potatoes aren't cooked.
Eun-yeong will have to give up
on the potatoes and just use radish.
-One minute.
-One minute left.
MASHED POTATOES ON THE JJAJANG RICE!
-Do you need the potatoes?
-Add oil as you work.
It's an emergency.
-A serious emergency.
-Oh, no.
STICKING RADISH LEAVES IN
-Just cover it up. Potatoes?
-Hurry up.
We might see the two worst dishes
of the show at the same time.
-Thirty seconds left.
-Thirty seconds!
Thirty seconds!
HE'S DRAWING SOMETHING
AT THIS POINT IN TIME?
-What's that?
-It doesn't look good.
-Balsamic sauce.
-Balsamic?
-Yes.
BALSAMIC SAUCE?
-There's the dinosaur.
-It's like a comic book.
THE DINOSAUR APPEARS
-Wait.
-What is this?
Which side is the head?
FOR THOSE OF YOU
WHO CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT LIKE WINTER…
Just like that.
THE REVIVAL OF A T-REX
The eye. Whatever. It's green onion.
GREEN ONION EYE WITH BALSAMIC SAUCE
What is that?
The eye. He's putting something on it.
THE EYE IS DONE
WATERMELON SEED NOSTRILS
-The round is over!
-Time's up!
-It's time!
-Ring the bell.
You cannot make anything new.
Look at that.
MAKING TEETH WITH MUSHROOMS
THERE HE IS, MY STEVEN SPIELBERG
PRESENTING HIS DISH
IN A WAY THAT KIDS WOULD DIE FOR
Poong finishes.
PLEASED
-I don't think this is happening.
-Why not?
-The potatoes didn't work…
-The potatoes?
…so they won't stick.
You called yourself
the KARINA of Chinese cuisine for nothing.
Eun-yeong just needs to stick
a few more radish pieces on it.
CORONA WITH HER HEAD DOWN…
-KARINA of Chinese cuisine.
-It's done.
You said you were KARINA. What is this?
A jellyfish.
A tomb?
That's all. Chef Eun-yeong finishes too!
PARK EUN-YEONG'S ARMAGEPORK IS DONE
THE 5-MINUTE CHECK IS DONE TOO
-That's the last bit.
-Whoa.
-It's convincing.
-It's like a T-Rex.
T-REX IS ON ITS WAY
Its arm is kind of long.
DISHES FROM COMICS ARE ON THEIR WAY!
Both dishes are finished.
THE TOUGHEST COOK-OFF YET
That was the toughest cook-off yet.
-We must give it to you.
-They had to focus on the visuals.
Both dishes were finished for KARINA.
As you can see,
it's a female dinosaur.
-How… What?
-I see. The lashes.
-I drew the lashes in.
-The eyelashes.
I wanted to make you
the main character of a cooking comic,
as you always should be.
-I woke up as a T-Rex?
-Yes.
I made you the main character.
-That's a loss for me.
-A dinosaur,
-but a girl.
-Yes, it's a female dinosaur.
Please try Poong's dish first.
A DINOSAUR DUMPLING
THAT'LL CAPTURE KARINA'S INTEREST
WEBTOON ARTIST KIM POONG'S KARINASAUR
EYE CONTACT
It's just the head.
Take a good look up close.
It's convincing.
You woke up and realized
you've become a T-Rex. That's it.
-Karinasaur.
-It's cute.
So where do I begin?
It doesn't matter where.
-It's all the same.
-Grab it.
-Just help yourself.
-But how?
The cheeks are delicious, right?
-The cheeks should be good.
-It's probably good.
I think the arm should be good.
Like jokbal.
CHECKING THE CUT
WAY TOO HARD
-It's…
-Like jokbal.
-I can't eat this.
-You can't?
-It's just bones.
-The legs should be good, not the arms.
Let me try this part.
-It's like sujebi.
-The cheeks are chubby.
-You put the filling in, right?
-Yes.
-Everywhere else has the filling inside.
-Dinosaur meat is red too?
-Because when you cut open a dinosaur…
-You're right.
-…it should be red.
-Yes.
CAPTURING EVERYONE'S ATTENTION
It would've been better
if ketchup shot out.
It's a shame.
HESITANT
I don't know why, but I feel bad.
KARINA is devouring the dinosaur.
You're now watching
KARINA feeding on a dinosaur.
That's the neck area.
THE GENRE OF THIS COMIC BOOK IS HORROR
-She's the first to eat a dinosaur.
-This is so odd.
Get some balsamic sauce on the dish
before you take a bite.
-This?
-She's supposed to eat that too?
-The sauce was there for a reason.
-Yes.
HESITANT
-I'll eat it now.
-Okay.
-You got this.
-She's eating a dinosaur.
SUDDENLY BECOMES A MUKBANG CHALLENGE
-You got this.
I wonder what dinosaur cheek is like.
CHEWS CAREFULLY
MMM
CHUCKLING
-Wait a second.
-So?
Is she trying to spit it out?
Do you need a tissue?
-Hmm?
-Yes?
-Must be good.
-Is it?
WHAT'S IT LIKE?
-It tastes like jeyuk-bokkeum.
-The spicy pork stir-fry?
Dinosaur jeyuk-bokkeum?
-Did you use meat?
-Yes.
I mixed pork neck and shrimp.
She's trying the muscle now.
-The muscle?
-It's good.
-It's good?
-It's there?
It's the color too.
GASP!
What are the teeth like?
Don't eat the teeth.
-They're raw mushrooms.
-You can't eat the teeth anyway.
I doubt people ate dinosaur teeth.
Are these watermelon seeds?
Yes, I made the nostrils
with watermelon seeds.
MAXIMUM LEVEL ON CREATIVITY
-One fell, so let me put it back.
-One of them dropped.
-You're right.
-It's just clogged up.
One of them fell.
-The skin.
-I'll be brave.
Dinosaurs are reptiles, right?
I'll try the arm.
There's no filling inside.
-It's probably bad.
-There's no filling in here?
A BITE OF THE ARM OUT OF CURIOSITY
You can always spit it out.
GIGGLING
-Not all cuts can be delicious.
-You're right.
-I'm sure there are good cuts.
-Like legs.
MMM
You know what? It's good.
-It is?
-Yes.
The filling's good, right?
It's like jeyuk-bokkeum over rice.
WHOA
-That's a success.
-You said you loved Korean food,
-so I took that route.
-It's intentional, right?
That dinosaur
must've eaten a pig before it died.
LOL
I'm sure dinosaurs tasted
something like jeyuk-bokkeum.
We'll try to imagine that.
The dinosaur wasn't wild.
-Was it farmed?
-It was farmed
and was often fed with pigs,
so it smells like it.
-While it was farmed?
-Farmed?
Did you find our conversation fun?
THAT'S RIGHT
WANTED TO BE INCLUDED
Just let me join in.
In the end, I ate myself, right?
THE AUTHOR'S INTENT?
Is that the case?
-It must be a horror comic.
-So I was a T-Rex in a previous life,
-and I ate myself in this life.
-That's right.
I honestly like this story.
COULD BE A MASTERPIECE
Now, next,
the work in question.
-"In question"?
-Chef Eun-yeong's dish.
A WHITE RADISH TREE
RIGHT OUT OF A COMIC BOOK
FILLED WITH DARK JJAJANG RICE
CHEF PARK EUN-YEONG'S ARMAGEPORK
-Wait, it's really pretty.
-Isn't it?
She used about two more minutes
trying to stick those in the potato.
So take that into consideration
before you make a decision.
-What does it symbolize?
-A flower, right?
Actually,
if the potatoes had cooked
all the way through,
I wanted to add more leaves
and make the tree look fuller.
But what I ended up making looks like
a tree from a horror comic book.
After all, you also have
an image as a warrior,
so please imagine a warrior
sitting on that flower
after defeating her enemy
in a brutal action comic book.
She tried her best.
She had been thinking about it all along.
It looks like something from a film
than a comic book.
Since she's a warrior,
it can be the egg where aliens hatch from.
AN ALIEN EGG?
Doesn't it look like that?
-She put jjajang rice inside, right?
-Yes.
Once she digs it up,
-it'll look like dirt.
-How exciting.
-So how about Exhuma?
-Exhuma.
That's great.
-She's eating dirt, then.
-Not bad.
How will she put the story together?
Think of it as a tree.
-How should I eat this? Just…
-Cut it in half?
Just tear it up and eat it.
LIKE HOW MY HEART IS TORN…
On top of the jjajang rice…
TEARING DOWN THE RADISH DISH
JJAJANG RICE SHOWS ITSELF
That jjajang rice was really good.
AGREED
It's like that old film
with the splitting grave, Public Cemetery.
I told you so. It looks like a grave.
-It feels like exhumation.
-You're right.
-Go with Korean Ghost Stories.
-Korean Ghost Stories.
Korean Jjajang Story.
She's trying to eat dirt!
"Eat dirt"?
She's like,
"Do I look like KARINA to you?"
DOES IT TASTE AS TERRIFYING AS IT LOOKS?
HEHE
-It's good.
-Is it?
-Why is she crying?
-Jjajang rice.
Must be sorrowfully delicious.
Sorrowfully delicious?
There's a grudge, like a nine-tailed fox
who passed away unfortunately.
HEHEHEHE
It passed away unfairly.
The story is forming as we speak.
IMMEDIATELY HAS ANOTHER BITE
MMM
HAPPY TO SEE HER
Are they good together?
Yes.
It goes well with the potato.
The aftertaste of the radish
leaves bitterness in my mouth,
and that's quite delicious.
RELIEVED
Is the potato undercooked?
-Let me try just the potato.
-Yes, just the potato.
YUM
She dug it up like it's a grave.
-The potato.
-Al dente.
LET'S SAY THAT IT'S AL DENTE
-Nice job.
-She added that texture intentionally.
But it's Korean Ghost Stories,
-so it goes well with the theme.
-It goes well?
Yes, even the texture.
Even the texture.
It's time to make a decision.
The dinosaur versus the nine-tailed fox.
Take one more look.
STARING
Press one to choose Park Eun-yeong
and two to choose Kim Poong.
Make your decision and press the button!
INDECISIVE
I did.
MADE HER DECISION
Let's find out her decision.
Show us!
THE RESULT
I Woke Up
and Found Myself in Cooking Comics.
Eun-yeong has won
all six rounds against him.
Will Poong finally win against her?
Or will Eun-yeong keep her winning streak?
KARINA's choice!
Who was it?
KARINA!
KIM POONG WINS
KIM POONG'S KARINASAUR WINS
Karinasaur!
Karinasaur wins.
THE VICTORY ROAR
VENTING THE SORROW
OF HIS 6 CONSECUTIVE LOSSES
That's Kim Poong.
-For the first time…
-Really?
-…in two years, he wins against Eun-yeong.
-Two years?
FIRST WIN AGAINST EUN-YEONG IN 2 YEARS
-It happened.
-It was about time.
I love dinosaurs,
so I was really moved
that he made one for me,
and I also loved the story.
LOVED THE KARINASAUR'S STORY TOO
Honestly speaking,
which one tasted better?
-Did it also…
-Even as food?
-It also tasted great?
-It was delicious.
It was such a rough journey.
When I first met Eun-yeong,
I never thought
she'd become my kryptonite.
I think this is…
Is Eun-yeong crying?
-What's wrong? Was it rough?
-First off,
I feel really bad for KARINA.
-Don't say that.
-I could've done better.
I knew it the moment you said
you were the KARINA of Chinese cuisine.
-It's karma.
-It was a stretch.
-I think they asked for Corona.
-Right?
NOW THE CORONA OF CHINESE CUISINE
-I think that's what they wanted. Corona?
-They wanted a Corona.
Please put a star on Kim Poong, KARINA!
Great job.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
He beats Eun-yeong and takes the star.
It's his eighth star.
Karinasaur.
And please take
the Chef & My Fridge tableware too.
We'll take a break for 15 minutes.
Don't you want to try that?
I am a bit curious.
Try it.
WALKING OVER TO TRY IT
TAKING A PICTURE TOO
So cute.
-Let me try it.
-Try it.
TRYING ARMAGEPORK FIRST
YUM
MMM!
IT'S SO GOOD, SHE TAKES ANOTHER BITE
NEXT TARGET, KARINASAUR
What do you think? Isn't it good?
It's good.
WINTER'S PLEASED TOO
PREPARING TO COOK
Let's roll. One, two, three.
Chef, please check the location.
IS THE LOCATION OF THE SHEET IMPORTANT?
CAREFULLY STICKING IT ON
The tension is so high.
SON JONG-WON IS BACK IN HIS WORK MODE
We have to peel the shrimp too.
How fast can you peel two?
Under a minute.
We'll have enough time
even if we stay laid-back,
-so there's no need to rush things.
-Yes, sir.
Gosh. This will be fun.
THE AIR IS DIFFERENT FROM USUAL
The second round cook-off
with KARINA's ingredients.
For this team round, our chefs have
teamed up with their own right-hand men.
The chemistry of an old couple
who's been married for 14 years,
Chef Choi Hyun-suk and Chef Kim Seon-yeop.
The good vibes doppelgänger chemistry,
Chef Son Jong-won and Chef Woo Do-hee.
This is going to be
the most intense team round of them all.
This is the real deal.
They work together around the year,
-so they must have great teamwork.
-Yes.
-Look how happy they seem.
It's so different from the time
when they teamed up with Poong.
Tell me about it.
Chef Seon-yeop seems quite nervous.
-How does it feel to stand there?
-He must be.
As I mentioned before,
we'll have to make
the best dish within 15 minutes,
so what I'm worried about
is if Chef Hyun-suk…
Stop acting like you're so nice.
He keeps grabbing him by the collar,
-and Seon-yeop keeps on flinching.
-It's too staged.
Anyway, we'll show you
the best teamwork.
AMBITIOUS AND CONFIDENT
He says nice things after getting grabbed.
PRACTICED OVER AND OVER FOR 14 YEARS
Everyone is laughing and joking around,
but only Chef Do-hee
stands there with a straight face.
He has kept that face all along.
He never smiled, not even once.
HE DID SMILE IN SECRET
Is the show not fun enough?
No, it's fun, and I'm doing my best.
-Yes, I'm watching it all.
-He knows what's up.
-He hasn't even eaten.
-Why not?
He told him to eat just a banana,
so that was all they ate.
-My gosh.
-For this round.
What are you the most worried about?
I don't know if we'll be able to finish
everything we prepared in time.
Do you find Jong-won hard to trust?
-No.
-You're worried, even with Jong-won here?
I don't want to be someone
who'll be a nuisance, so I'll do my best.
-But this guy is already "someone."
-We already have someone.
He's already someone.
Chef Do-hee claimed
that he knows what Jong-won is thinking
from even the smallest head tilt he makes.
TELEPATHIC
-Yes.
-Really?
I've become used to figuring out
what he's thinking over my time with him.
I can always tell what he needs.
Chef Seon-yeop,
you can also do the same, right?
Try to guess what this means.
-Destroy Kim Poong.
-Correct.
-He can tell.
-"Destroy Kim Poong."
PLEASED
So 14 years does that.
There was an intel leak
from Chef Jong-won's side.
He made a timetable
-for this 15-minute cook-off.
-What?
-For this?
-We'll show you.
You took a picture?
-There it is.
-It's true!
Did you split up 15 minutes into minutes?
-It's in 30-second intervals.
-In 30 seconds?
-Thirty seconds?
-Can you stick to it?
I was going to make it 15 seconds,
but I considered the variables
and stuck with 30 seconds.
-That side is Woo, and that's Son?
-You're right.
-They each have different tasks to do.
-Wow.
We'll show you
what Chef Hyun-suk is working with.
-We have a timetable?
-You have one?
No, this team doesn't have one.
-They don't.
-Do you not have a plan?
-They don't need one.
It's not that.
We've worked together for a long time.
Once we have the recipe,
we can work systematically yet smoothly
as we both ride in the flow.
-In the flow.
-In the flow?
The flow could get blocked.
What then? Do you have a plan B?
If it gets blocked…
WAVES
SHOWS OFF HIS CHEEKY WAVES
-Then we'll flow to the other side.
-The other side.
TEAM CHOI: SHRIMP, MILK, TSUYU,
GOMTANG RAMYEON SOUP BASE, RED WINE
RIB EYE, WATERMELON, CHAMPAGNE,
LEMON JUICE, RUBY KIWI, AND MORE
The name of our dish is this.
KARINA,
This Is Choi-Seon's Best.
Like "the best," choeseon.
"Choi" Hyun-suk and Kim "Seon"-yeop.
KARINA, THIS IS CHOI-SEON'S BEST
First, for the lemonade,
since you seem to enjoy alcohol,
we're going to make lemonade for adults.
Also, you didn't have
lobster in your fridge,
but as the alchemists of culinary arts,
Team Chef Choi,
will make it for you.
You'll make lobster without lobster?
You can't make the lobster
like he did with the dinosaur.
You can't do that.
I guess he was inspired by me.
I put up with everything so far,
but that triggered me.
BECAUSE DINOSAURS ARE REALLY STRONG
Well, if he can make a dinosaur,
I'm sure you can make a lobster.
TEAM SON: SHRIMP, ZUCCHINI,
LEMON, CARROT, CELERY, ROMAINE
LANGOUSTINE SOUP, MILK,
POTATO, BEEF TENDERLOIN, AND MORE
Up against them are Chef Jong-won
and Chef Do-hee. What are you making?
We made an acrostic poem
with the syllables of "lemon."
An acrostic poem? That's creative.
You're quite the entertainer.
Let us start you off.
-Like a toast.
-I'll do it.
-Like a toast?
-All right. I'll start you off.
-Le.
-Lemonade…
-And KARINA Are…
-Mon.
-…Monumental for Life.
MELTED HER HEART
THAT WAS A NICE TOAST
They already get points for that name.
KARINA looks very pleased.
THE FRUIT OF THEIR PRACTICE
-So what is this dish?
-Oh, right.
-"Oh, right."
-We get the name.
-Monumental.
-What's the recipe?
First, we'll use zucchini
and shrimp to make mousse.
-Zucchini.
-We also found
canned langoustine stock,
so we'll make sauce with that.
Also, we'll make steak
topped with lemon pepper,
and lastly, lemon hwachae,
a total of three dishes.
-Chef Hyun-suk.
-Yes?
Shouldn't you also do an acrostic poem?
They already got some points.
KARINA melted a little.
If they worked together for 14 years,
-I'm sure they'll be better.
-Yes, of course.
HAVING FUN HEART
I mean, 14 years.
They'll do this much better
-than the team before.
-Of course.
-I wonder who'll do the first part.
-The first part?
-It's better to go first.
-Let's do it.
It's for Choi-Seon. One, two, three.
-Choi.
Choi Hyun-suk and other chefs' presence
is such an honor for me.
-That's nice.
-I'm not done yet.
Oh?
-And then?
-But Webtoon Artist Kim Poong.
-Suddenly I'm in it?
-"But Webtoon Artist Kim Poong."
That was it for the first syllable.
-Seon.
It's not,
"Seon-yeop will take you out," right?
-Seon.
It's going to be really funny.
-It'll be funny.
-Seon.
I'm so excited.
Lights down, please.
Let's start cooking!
-He couldn't finish it.
-What a shame.
Do, "Seon-yeop will teach you a lesson."
-Seon.
-Seon-yeop will teach you a lesson.
STILL PLEASED
WAS THAT TRULY YOUR BEST?
Now, a round just for KARINA.
Lights down, please.
Timer, please.
ONLY ONE TEAM WILL RISE ABOVE!
A never-before-seen cook-off,
the first time in the show's history.
-Wow.
They'll play as a team
with their right-hand men.
Hyun-suk and Seon-yeop will prove
the 14 years they spent together.
The chefs who are passionate
about both cooking and team dinners,
Jong-won and Do-hee are up against them.
The first team round
with the chefs' right-hand men!
Which team will be the winner?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
WOW!
TEAM SON MOVES FAST!
Let's see what they do.
1. MAKE SYRUP BY BOILING WATER AND SUGAR
-Jong-won and Do-hee divided the tasks.
-Yes.
Their timetable is planned out
in 30-second intervals.
2. MAKE SHRIMP MOUSSE BY GRINDING
SHRIMP, STARCH WATER, AND EGG WHITES
Jong-won chops the zucchini.
Their plans
are in 30-second intervals.
-I don't know who to look at.
-Right? I'm busy looking at everyone.
Seon-yeop preps shrimp.
-Hyun-suk is on eggs.
-Eggs.
He's doing the easier job.
Chef Seon-yeop, give me an order
if you need me to do something.
I guess Seon-yeop is the main chef.
-Give me the mousse right away.
-Yes, sir.
-Mousse and diced veggies.
It's been 30 seconds!
ALREADY?
-Already? Will they move on?
-It's already been 30 seconds.
They'll have to move on every 30 seconds.
3. MIX SHRIMP MOUSSE
WITH LEMON ZEST AND STARCH
4. SLICE ZUCCHINI THINLY
-Spin that.
-Yes, Chef.
-Another 30.
-That was another 30 seconds.
-It's been a minute already.
-Another 30 seconds!
-They're still on the first task.
-The first task.
-It's been a minute.
-They've been doing that for a minute.
THE GOOD VIBES DOPPELGÄNGERS
-Spin that.
-Yes, Chef.
SHRIMP MOUSSE, FINISHED
-Dice the veggies and grind the pepper.
-Yes, Chef.
GIVING ACCURATE ORDERS!
One, two, three.
GIVING ACCURATE ORDERS?!
-They just salted the food!
-I knew it.
Salty and sweet
-They prepared something too.
-The salt cross.
KARINA asked you
to salt her food many times.
-Is Chef Hyun-suk doing the busywork?
-I think so.
Seon-yeop seems to be doing the main job.
They said they'd make lobster,
so I have a feeling
they'll do it with shrimp.
Seon-yeop is trying to create
something from nothing!
-By stacking layers of shrimp?
-Yes, I think that's it.
WOW
Just make one if you have no time.
-I'll make just two.
-Hmm?
I'll make two.
Jong-won and Do-hee
are working on vegetables.
Carrot and zucchini.
Do-hee is quite fast too.
DICE ONION, CARROT, CELERY
-Are you done dicing?
-Sorry?
-How much longer do you need?
-Thirty seconds, Chef.
ONLY 30 SECONDS
TO DICE ONION, CARROT, AND CELERY?
-I'm done dicing, Chef.
-Okay.
CARROT, ONION, CELERY
ONION
It's hard to tell what's going on
with two chefs on each side.
Chef Seon-yeop.
-Don't be nervous. We got this.
-Yes.
Chef Seon-yeop, trust me.
Hyun-suk keeps talking to Seon-yeop.
They'll fill shrimp with shrimp.
-Minced shrimp.
-What's that?
-What is it, Hyun-suk?
Why are you sifting the shrimp?
He'll sift it, put it on the shrimp,
and make lobster shapes.
-Wow.
-So he needs that to make the lobster.
We're here to show our best performance,
which means fine dining-like
soft texture is important.
The texture, the presentation,
the taste, and the flavor.
We won't miss anything.
That's him.
3. SIFT THE SHRIMP PASTE
Aren't taste and flavor the same thing?
The savoriness.
-The savoriness.
-Right.
-Chef Jong-won's making something.
-He's making something
-with tweezers.
-A zucchini flower filled with shrimp.
-Zucchini flower?
-Whoa.
Shrimp and zucchini flower?
That's a dinosaur eye.
-Is it a dinosaur?
-A dinosaur eye, right?
He must've been inspired.
-He inspires me often.
-How delicate.
-He's very detailed.
-Like that?
-No one seems confused.
-Both teams have great teamwork.
-Wow. How do they do that?
-The soup base.
He'll probably do his best to create
lobster's flavor and texture.
When she tries it,
-she can't go, "It's a shrimp."
-She shouldn't.
-She can't.
-That's not good.
-You're right.
-It should look similar too.
Yes, of course.
She didn't have a lobster,
so can they really make it?
-Is this enough, Chef?
-What?
I TRUST YOU!
FINISHING UP BY ROLLING IT IN COOKING FOIL
Huh?
Gomtang ramyeon?
-Ramyeon soup base.
-MSG! Ramyeon soup base.
-I love it.
-He said he'd make gravy with that.
It's made with beef bones anyway,
just like how gomtang
is made with beef bone broth.
-But gravy has to be darker in color.
-He'll make it happen.
-It's gomtang ramyeon soup base.
-Will he boil the soup base?
-Let's boil down wine.
-He's boiling it.
GOMTANG RAMYEON SOUP,
RED WINE, SIMPLE SYRUP
JONG-WON IS DONE MAKING SYRUP
-Simple syrup.
-Yes, Chef.
I'll crush the pepper.
We'll crush the pepper,
then coat the steak before grilling it.
Like pepper sauce?
AH-HA!
Why can't you use a pepper grinder?
The pieces need to be bigger
to make the pepper sauce.
-I see.
-Crushing.
He's not using a grinder.
-The aroma is stronger that way too.
-I see.
OPENS THE STEAMER
It's going in.
Zucchini enters the steamer.
-Zucchini enters the steamer.
-Okay.
COME ON!
CARROT & ONION & CELERY
Ten minutes.
Bisque.
-Langoustine bisque.
It's been five minutes,
Jong-won and Do-hee.
-It's gravy versus bisque.
-Yes, gravy versus bisque.
What was that?
THE SALT YOU ORDERED!
WAS THIS WHAT HE MEANT
BY CLEANING UP AFTER HIS MESS?
They came prepared.
They're just… Gosh.
They prepared that to win aespa's favor.
Hyun-suk and Seon-yeop
don't forget to put on a performance.
I think they just won
a few points from her.
8. GRILL RIB EYE IN A PAN
TEAM SON STARTS ON THEIR SECOND DISH
-How long will pommes soufflées take?
-Pommes soufflées?
Just one minute, Chef.
-He's patting the potato slices dry.
-Will he fry those?
Will he fry those?
Chef Do-hee, will you fry those?
Yes, Chef.
He just said, "Yes, Chef."
-Did he call me a chef?
-He did.
Thank you, Chef!
Chef Do-hee.
No one has ever called me that before.
Whenever Jong-won said something,
Do-hee kept answering, "Yes, Chef,"
in a soft voice.
It's amazing that a chef
who came for the first time can respond.
-It means he can hear you.
-It does.
-It also means he can hear Chef Jong-won.
-That's true.
Better than me. I couldn't respond.
-He'll make them puffy.
-The potato garnish he's making
will look like puffy balloons.
-By sticking them together?
-They'll puff up.
It's tough to make.
Careful. It's the syrup.
SHRIMP ROLL
What did you put in, Seon-yeop?
The shrimp cake.
He can respond too.
-He can.
-Egg yolks.
They're listening to their head chefs.
Did you add salt?
No.
COARSELY GROUND BLACK PEPPER
SALT, LEMON ZEST
He's tying the tenderloin
and turning it into a medal
-to keep the shape together.
-There's the steak.
He's working on the steak.
Hyun-suk is grilling meat too.
PERFECT CRUST!
-That's nicely done.
-It looks delicious.
Jong-won's steak looks a bit prettier.
He's using tenderloin,
and I think that's strip loin.
He's about to deep-fry them.
-It's 183°C. Go.
-He's deep-frying.
I hope those turn out nicely.
Those are hard to make.
-What's hard?
-Deep-frying those.
It's not hard.
-They have to get puffy.
-They have to puff up.
-The potatoes?
-Yes.
It's tough to do.
-Do-hee is up for a tough task.
-Careful.
Like tiny balloons.
-Precisely.
-But with potatoes.
-They're getting puffy.
-It's their steak garnish.
Do-hee shows off his technique!
He needs to pour oil on top
to help them get puffier.
He made the potato pieces puff up.
Do-hee, the bread is in.
-I haven't done it.
-I did.
Oui.
"Oui, Chef."
-Oui?
-Oui, Chef. It's yes in French.
It means yes?
-That's tough to do.
-Team Jong-won shows a good technique.
-They look good.
-I knew it.
Hyun-suk and Seon-yeop
are each doing their own thing.
QUIETLY PREPARING THE WATERMELON GARNISH
9. CHOP WATERMELON INTO A BAR
AND GRILL IN BUTTER
It smells like a fine dining restaurant.
CHUCKLING
It smells like it.
May I recite another acrostic poem?
-An acrostic poem? With what?
-All of a sudden?
Please start me off.
What's the word?
-Lemon?
-Lemon, please.
SPRINKLING SALT!
WHAT'S THIS NOW?
Salt!
CUTTING OFF THE ACROSTIC POEM!
-He was about to do the poem!
-He cuts the poem off!
THIS IS HILARIOUS
He didn't want to lose attention.
BASTING WITH BUTTER
13. COOK THE TENDERLOIN IN THE OVEN
I thought Sung-jun would be too talkative,
-so I had prepared it for him.
-What is it?
-One, two, three. Le!
-Le!
Lemon, hold it.
-One, two, three. Mon!
-Mon!
Monster.
CAUGHT OFF GUARD
He had that prepared.
That was random.
-That was so random.
-So random.
-That was awful.
-Sung-jun suddenly got attacked.
He was caught off guard.
I prepared it,
so I wanted to use it on anyone.
-With that lemon.
-He's just a monster with a lemon.
It's hard to stop late bloomers.
"Lemon, hold this. You monster."
Sorry, Sung-jun.
Jong-won and Do-hee couple…
"Couple"?
Not only are they good at cooking,
but they're funny too.
They're funny and have good teamwork too.
Six minutes left!
-There's no time.
-Six minutes.
You should start wrapping up.
-Did they get puffy? Wow.
-Two pieces.
They became puffy.
-Did you add salt?
-I didn't.
-Take this.
-Okay.
COVERING
SEON-YEOP STRAINS MELTED BUTTER
COOL DOWN, PLEASE
Is Chef Seon-yeop
making mayonnaise?
-Is that mayo?
-I'm making hollandaise.
-Hollandaise?
-Hollandaise.
These dishes
all require lots of techniques.
-We have no idea what's going on now.
-Right?
ALL RIGHT
PUTTING BUTTER INTO A SYRINGE
LOCKED IN
WHAT'S THIS TOOL FOR?
-What's that? What's he doing?
-What is that, Do-hee?
-Is that butter?
-Butter.
-You can do that?
-He squeezed butter out.
WOW…
-How cool.
-It looks like ribbon.
I want that thing too.
-It's like knife-cut noodles.
-Is that a flower?
Do-hee makes that
to capture the lady's heart.
That's so pretty.
Are you intrigued, KARINA?
SO INTRIGUED
-How pretty.
-That's so pretty.
15. MAKE FLOWER BUTTER
-I want that thing too.
-That's nice.
Five minutes left.
Jung-hwan, please go to the kitchen.
It's too crowded over there.
Which team has better teamwork?
It's crowded.
-It's so crowded over here.
-Four minutes left.
Chef Do-hee squeezes a lemon.
16. MIX SYRUP AND LEMON JUICE
Hey, Chef Jong-won.
ZUCCHINI SHRIMP MOUSSE, FINISHED
There are so many sauces.
There are, right?
Yes, too many. It's so complicated here.
-That thing.
-He's cooking watermelon.
-Is that watermelon?
-Yes.
-Watermelon?
-He's still cooking the steak.
-He adds balsamic vinegar.
-Balsamic vinegar.
Watermelon and balsamic.
-They work well as a team.
-Jung-hwan!
Can you try Seon-yeop's sauce?
It's hollandaise.
-Okay!
-Let me try this.
Jung-hwan!
Is that Choi-Seon's best?
-This is the best!
-Is it really?
EXCITED
-It's great.
-Nothing wrong with it?
It's salty, and full of umami.
SCALLIONS
-They kept throwing salt in.
-They did.
-Wait, what about the lobster?
-The steamer.
It's in the steamer?
I hope it turns out well.
It tasted very nice.
There's a feel to it.
It must be salty and delicious.
Seon-yeop's adding butter now.
I'll hollow out the lemon.
-Four minutes, Do-hee.
-Yes, Chef.
-And the Parisian cut.
-Oui.
HOLLOWING OUT THE LEMON!
MELON & MANGO
-Cut these out.
-Oui.
I'll finish these and crush ice.
Melon?
PARISIAN CUT: FINE DINING TECHNIQUE
TO SCOOP FRUITS AND VEGGIES INTO SPHERES
MISSION COMPLETE!
I'll crush the ice, Chef.
Crush the ice first
-and fill the plate.
-Oui.
Three minutes left!
He crushed some ice too.
Jong-won and Do-hee
are only prepping the ingredients.
17. CRUSH ICE, FILL A CUP,
TOP IT WITH HOLLOWED-OUT LEMON
The bisque sauce.
The bisque sauce. This one?
-It's this one.
-They look the same.
-The farther one?
-It's the same.
-Try one.
They're different.
-Try it, Jung-hwan.
-Oh, no.
-They're the same. Which one should I try?
-They're different.
-They're different?
-Try both.
-Both?
-They're very different.
The farther one first, then.
The sauce from the farther pot.
Will KARINA find the sauce monumental?
ANTICIPATION
-It's monumental!
-Whoa!
-The sauce's monumental.
-Monumental.
It's so good.
Was that the bisque?
It has that
classic instant cream soup flavor.
WAVES
"I need your attention."
HYUN-SUK'S MOTTO:
A DISH LIKE A COMEDY FILM!
WHAT'S HE SHAKING EXCITEDLY?
KARINA'S FAVORITE, RUBY KIWI
AND THE MAIN INGREDIENT, LEMON!
14. SHAKE RUBY KIWI, LEMON JUICE,
AND ICE IN A COCKTAIL SHAKER
It has that
classic instant cream soup flavor.
WAVES
"I need your attention."
-Mister.
-Hyun-suk!
He doesn't forget
to create an entertaining moment.
I'm about to faint.
-Lemonade.
-So funny.
He's serious about these performances.
-He kept doing the wave.
-Jung-hwan!
I think that's the lobster.
Is this lobster?
Try this piece.
FILMING FIRST
How did it turn out like lobster?
Hey, it's lobster!
It's lobster!
Hey, it looks like one.
CHOI-SEON'S MAGIC!
-It's lobster.
-She didn't have it.
LOOKS LIKE PLUMP LOBSTER MEAT
Let me have a taste.
-The tip.
-Is it like lobster?
-Does it taste like lobster?
-Does it?
-This is insane. It's lobster.
-It is?
-It's lobster!
THE MAGIC FOOLED BOTH HIS EYES AND PALATE
It has the texture of a "matster,"
I mean, lobster too.
DID YOU JUST CALL ME?
-This is amazing.
-"Matster."
So you can make this texture?
He finished making the lobster.
A minute and 40 seconds.
Bisque is ready.
This could make
Jong-won and Do-hee anxious.
KARINA, it'll be so hard to choose.
-Oh, no.
-The sauce is already crazy.
THE ZUCCHINI SHRIMP MOUSSE
COOKED IN THE STEAMER
Look at the details he added.
Look at them move as a team.
-This is what it takes.
-It's incredible.
This is what it takes
to be in fine dining.
-Make the base.
-Yes, sir.
It's such a shame
that she'll have to choose only one team.
Where's the butter?
Already in there, sir.
It's in the box.
-Here's the bread.
-Steak.
-Should I cut the bread? Romaine?
-Cut the romaine.
It's busy here!
Do-hee cuts lettuce.
-Do-hee.
-Yes, Chef.
Make lemonade now.
It's right here.
WHEN DID YOU GET IT DONE?
-Did you add lemon juice?
-I did.
RETURNS TO HIS TASK
The lemonade?
-The lemonade.
-He said he'd add alcohol.
I love the color.
Champagne.
16. MIX CHAMPAGNE WITH RUBY KIWI LEMONADE
This is fascinating.
I love the color.
One minute left. The last minute!
Only a minute left.
One minute!
Zero mistakes are made.
They do everything perfectly.
-They're on the same wavelength.
-Right?
And when one asks something
even without looking,
-the other one responds.
-Right?
AMAZED FOR THE 32,645TH TIME
-Kiwi.
-Can you take this?
-The lemonade is done.
-It's the lemonade.
-It's done.
-It's ready.
-Is that a cocktail?
-It's kiwi-colored.
Pour a little more champagne.
That's the lemonade?
FALLS!
-Kiwi!
-It fell!
-The kiwi fell down.
-Put a new one.
-It went inside.
-It's supposed to be in there.
-It is?
-Be quiet.
THE KIWI SUBMERGED IN THE LEMONADE
It's hot. Be careful.
REMOVING THE STRING
LEMON PEPPER STEAK IS DONE!
-Twenty seconds!
-Oh, no.
-Please wrap up now.
-Yes, wrap up the steak and the sauce.
They're plating it now.
-Ten seconds remain!
-Ten seconds.
SERVING LOBSTER IN HOLLANDAISE
WOO DO-HEE'S LAST 10 SECONDS!
20. PUT MELON, MANGO BALLS IN THE LEMON,
THEN POUR LEMONADE TO MAKE HWACHAE
CHOI HYUN-SUK'S LAST 10 SECONDS!
18. POUR GRAVY NEXT TO
RIB EYE STEAK AND GRILLED WATERMELON
Ring the bell.
HYUN-SUK AND SEON-YEOP FINISH FIRST!
-Two.
SON JONG-WON'S LAST 20 SECONDS!
They're plating it now.
Chef Jong-won pours
the steak sauce on top.
21. TOP STEAK WITH LEMON HAYASHI SAUCE,
POMMES SOUFFLÉES, AND ROMAINE
-Eight. Seven.
-Seven.
-Six. Five.
22. POUR LANGOUSTINE BISQUE SAUCE
ALONGSIDE THE MOUSSE
-Jong-won and Do-hee are done too.
-Jong-won's done.
That was amazing.
Great work.
EVEN THE SPECTATORS FEEL DRAINED
-These are…
-It's crazy.
That was simply incredible.
Look at him sweating.
So this is what it takes.
-Great work, chefs.
-Look at them sweating.
Smells like a fine dining restaurant.
Please get rid of that kiwi.
-Let's go.
-Everything has been made.
It smells so good.
THE HIGHEST QUALITY DISHES YET!
-They did this in 15 minutes.
-Watermelon?
-Wait, is this the lobster?
-He really did it.
These were all made for KARINA's order,
"LEMONADE."
The team round was different, right?
Any thoughts?
It was so interesting,
like I was watching a masterpiece.
It was such an honor.
-They showed great teamwork.
-Yes.
Team Hyun-suk,
did everything go as planned?
There were a few tasks we had to do,
but Chef Seon-yeop became too nervous
-and missed about three.
-Three tasks?
But I patched everything up
and brought us to the end.
WHOA…
Most people wouldn't say that.
Seon-yeop already mentioned
that I tend to fish for praise.
-He's honest about it.
-He is.
What about you, Chef Jong-won?
He did even better than I thought.
I knew he could do it.
Let me go again.
A BIG LAUGH
Chef Seon-yeop did better than I thought.
Seon-yeop, what was it like?
Did it go well?
I wanted to make good dishes
within 15 minutes
and clean up everything too.
-As expected, Jong-won's counter is clean.
-It is.
But I couldn't clean up.
-When did he do that?
-Right?
Chef Hyun-suk's team finished first.
KARINA, This Is Choi-Seon's Best.
SHRIMP APPETIZER TURNED INTO LOBSTER
STEAK SERVED WITH GRILLED WATERMELON
WITH LEMONADE COCKTAIL,
FEATURING RUBY KIWI
HYUN-SUK & SEON-YEOP'S
KARINA, THIS IS CHOI-SEON'S BEST
-You wanted food paired with lemonade…
-Thank you.
-…but you got a red drink.
-Yes.
I made it with lemon and sparkling water,
so it's definitely lemonade,
but I also made it
with ruby kiwi, which you like.
-Lastly, I added some champagne.
-I see.
It'll pair very nicely
with everything you see there.
-What first?
-Try the appetizer,
-the lobster, and then the steak.
-The lobster.
-It looks like an actual lobster.
-But she didn't have one.
It looks just like it.
Call me the flavor alchemist.
-He is like an alchemist.
-I knew it.
-I'm nervous. Okay.
-Look at it too.
Will it taste like lobster too?
WILL IT TASTE LIKE ACTUAL LOBSTER?
It definitely looks like lobster.
-Mmm!
-Huh?
-Is it shrimp?
-Lobster?
-It's lobster.
-It is?
AMAZED
How did he do that?
THANK YOU
Wow.
-This is so weird.
-How did they do that?
Is it not like shrimp?
I'm eating this knowing it's shrimp,
but it still tastes like lobster.
That means he made it perfectly.
Wow.
-So good.
-There's one more?
-I wonder what the sauce is like.
-That's amazing.
This sauce is so good.
-Hollandaise.
-The sauce is good?
-Was it hollandaise?
-Hollandaise with lemon.
That's Chef Seon-yeop's sauce.
GIGGLE
I love how refreshing it is.
It goes so well with this lobster shrimp.
It's so good.
-Try the lemonade now.
-The lemonade.
Have a sip of it.
-Champagne lemonade.
-Looks good.
-Mmm.
-What's it like?
Is it something you like?
It feels like I'm drinking
a very refreshing champagne.
It's like I'm at the beach.
Where?
-Somewhere in Hawaii.
-Hawaii.
-Her outfit goes so well with Hawaii.
-It does.
It's as if
she's at a restaurant in Hawaii.
-It's so good. What do I start with?
-She had a sip of the drink.
Try the steak with sauce
and have the watermelon as a garnish.
-Watermelon.
-That's watermelon?
THE STEAK CUTS EASILY
Try them separately, and then together.
I'll try them separately first.
WE CAN FEEL THE TASTE WITHOUT WORDS
-Those guys are good at making steak.
-They are.
It's so delicious.
-That's watermelon.
-Sounds good.
MMM
-Whoa.
-I'm curious.
Tell us what it tastes like.
I've never had watermelon like this,
but it goes well with steak.
-He grilled it in balsamic sauce.
-Right.
It doesn't taste too sweet,
but it only retained the refreshing aroma
and the crunchy texture.
These go so well together.
I can't really eat too much beef,
but I could eat many servings of this.
Another sip of the cocktail.
AUTOMATICALLY REACHES OUT FOR LEMONADE
It's as if she's enjoying a meal
on the Waikiki beach.
Next up, Jong-won and Do-hee's dish,
Lemonade And KARINA Are
Monumental for Life.
LEMONY ZUCCHINI SHRIMP MOUSSE
LEMON PEPPER STEAK WITH POMMES SOUFFLÉES
AND LEMONADE HWACHAE AS DESSERT
JONG-WON & DO-HEE'S LEMONADE AND KARINA
ARE MONUMENTAL FOR LIFE
Where should I begin?
Cut into the shrimp mousse with a spoon
-and try it with the soup.
-Whoa.
That will compare to the lobster.
-You're right.
-The shrimp dishes.
Shrimp versus shrimp.
Who's going to take the lead?
-I'll try it.
-The sauce is different.
SNIFF
Bisque versus gravy.
-Hollandaise.
It must be good.
Is it different?
These are
definitely shrimp-flavored
and lobster-flavored.
Does it taste like shrimp?
What could it be?
Something about it smells good.
-The smell? What's it like?
-It smells good?
That fragrant smell
keeps lingering in my nose as I eat.
-I brought it out by adding lemon juice…
-Lemon.
…and I used zucchini
for the crunchy texture.
You'll also see some bread next to you.
Try dipping it in the sauce.
Eat the bread with the sauce.
That's your bread.
KARINA is in for a treat.
Whoa.
-It tastes like a whole new dish.
-Really?
Chef Do-hee prepared
a little present for you, KARINA.
What? What is it?
That tiny box contains a ring.
-A ring?
-Where?
-You'll find butter inside.
FLOWER BUTTER RING HIDDEN IN THE BOX
-He made a flower with butter.
-From the start?
-He made a flower.
-How sweet of him.
He knows what women love.
TAKING A BITE WITH FLOWER BUTTER
AND BISQUE SAUCE ON TOP
MMM
-It's definitely delicious.
-Is that so?
It looks good.
What's next?
-The steak.
Try it with lots of sauce.
What are those Go stones on top?
Pommes soufflées,
-made by stacking potatoes.
-He had a technique for it.
-Whoa!
-It's hard to make.
That's how you made those?
WHAT'S THE STEAK LIKE?
-It must be good.
-It has to be.
I'm hungry.
Ground pepper?
-He topped the steak with ground pepper.
-With the mortar?
I love the ground pepper.
-It's different.
-He crushed it himself.
Also, I didn't just bite into the steak.
I had a fluffy bite
of this potato garnish as well,
which adds the fun to the texture.
And then the ground pepper pops
to leave behind an aroma.
Lastly, the piece of romaine
balances out the greasiness.
-Pepper and potato.
-Nice pair.
Do-hee did it all.
-It's good.
-I see.
When can she have the lemonade?
-Enjoy it after the steak, at the end.
-At the end.
I called it hwachae,
but it's filled with lemonade inside,
along with fruit that you love.
-Inside?
-In there?
COLORFUL
-These are so…
-My gosh.
-I saw him scooping stuff up.
-Right?
-Melon and… Mango.
-Melon and probably mango.
-It's so pretty.
-That's what he was doing.
WHAT'S THE LEMONADE HWACHAE LIKE?
It must be refreshing.
They know how to capture her heart.
IT MUST BE GOOD
Wow.
ANOTHER BITE
-She'd love it.
-She has to.
Wow.
It's by far one of the best hwachae
I have ever had.
-One of the best?
-It's that good?
It just refreshed me
from everything I just had.
FEELS PROUD
It's good.
-Do you have some for WINTER?
-Sure.
Please share some with her.
PULLING OUT
Min-jeong.
SMILING LIKE HE'S THEIR DAD
Act like you're eating it.
-Like that.
-Act like it.
Pretend like
you're drinking from the straw.
OOH
Done.
WAS AT CHEF & MY FRIDGE
WINTER, please try
Hyun-suk and Seon-yeop's dishes first.
Lobster.
LOBSTER SHRIMP FIRST
Lobster made with shrimp?
YUM
-Mmm?
-Doesn't it taste like lobster?
-It's really like lobster.
-It is?
Really?
It really is,
and it's sour.
-It must be the hollandaise.
-Must be the sauce.
Next, steak with watermelon.
Those chefs are proud of their steaks.
Isn't it good?
EXCHANGING SIGNALS AGAIN
So you have to eat them together?
-Yes.
-I see.
-At once.
-I can make this at home. It's not hard.
-The watermelon?
-I can just cook it with steak.
It must be different in some way.
-She finished it all.
-She's done.
She must've waited a while.
I can't press
two buttons at the same time, can I?
-You have to choose just one.
-That's shrimp.
-Now, Chef Jong-won's dishes.
-Chef Jong-won's dishes.
-The shrimp.
-That's shrimp.
A HUGE SMILE
I get why she called this shrimp.
It does taste different
from that lobster shrimp.
That sauce is made with langoustine,
something more exclusive than lobster.
EMBARRASSED
-He feels anxious.
-Anyway, you had it
in your fridge, and you were
the first one who had this can.
-Next, the steak.
-That's a great mix too.
-It's tenderloin.
-Tenderloin steak.
They can compare directly
because you both made steak.
Unlike Chef Hyun-suk's steak,
it has many different flavors.
-There are lots of aromas too.
-Aromas.
-Ground pepper.
-Lemon zest.
It feels richer.
But that one…
Tasted poor?
Did it taste poor?
IT'S A MISUNDERSTANDING, GRANDPA
-I wouldn't be able to choose.
-No?
I'd try to push both at once.
-She just said that.
-I asked, "Can I press both at once?"
Can you just press both?
You're not allowed to do that.
Not a single person left without choosing.
Are you serious?
Not even once.
The one you choose will take the star.
Press one for Jong-won and Do-hee,
and two for Hyun-suk and Seon-yeop.
-Which leader will get to save his face?
-After all, they both tried hard.
Please stop.
You keep saying…
Make your decision.
-It must be heartbreaking.
-You're right.
It's hard to choose.
It's about your personal preference.
Make your decision.
I'll focus solely on the order
to make the decision.
-Solely on the order?
-The order?
-Okay.
-Did you press one?
I couldn't do that.
-She chose one.
-She did?
-She did.
-Oh, gosh! I want to cut my fingers off.
-All right.
-What now?
Let's find out!
KARINA's choice.
-I can't watch this.
-I'm going home.
Their release, "LEMONADE" was a hit.
So which set of dishes
went better with lemonade?
Is it Hyun-suk and Seon-yeop?
Or is it Jong-won and Do-hee?
-Not a single person has made a mistake.
-I'm nervous too.
This is awful.
I want to cut off my fingers.
I can't watch this.
Which one did KARINA choose?
Gosh.
The "LEMONADE" round. Was it Choi-Seon?
Or was it Lemon?
Who did she choose?
CHOI HYUN-SUK AND KIM SEON-YEOP WIN
HYUN-SUK AND SEON-YEOP'S
KARINA, THIS IS CHOI-SEON'S BEST WINS
Hyun-suk and Seon-yeop!
EVERYONE DID THEIR BEST
REGARDLESS OF THE RESULT
-Why did you choose them?
-I chose them because…
Well, when I had my first bite,
Chef Son's dishes had
many more wow factors.
But the dishes
that went much better with lemonade
were Chef Hyun-suk's.
It made me want to go
back and forth between the dishes.
-So it was how they paired.
-How they paired.
She wanted to have it with the meal
instead of having it as dessert.
Nothing beats the original cast.
CAN'T HIDE HIS SMILE
Look at his face.
-He can't hide how he feels.
-My gosh.
Fourteen years is hard to beat.
Let's hear from Chef Seon-yeop too.
I should've done my best to assist him,
but I ended up receiving his help.
Thank you very much
for giving me this great memory.
Don't say that.
I'm only here
as your supporter, Seon-yeop.
It must be a bummer, Jong-won.
Any thoughts?
I'm very happy for this team round
that I got to experience
with Do-hee and Seon-yeop.
The reason why Chef Hyun-suk
and I could be loved this much
is all thanks to our teams
who stay by our side
and work quietly with us.
So it was quite meaningful
that I got to cook with my teammate.
-Yes, and we witnessed it together.
-We did.
Please put the stars
on Team Hyun-suk, KARINA!
Great job.
GREAT JOB, EVERYONE
Put them on, KARINA.
Hyun-suk takes his seventh star!
Congratulations.
Also, the tableware set.
COMING UP: PREVIEW FOR
CHANG HANG-JUN & J.Y. PARK'S EPISODE
Congratulations!
Today's fridge owners are
Chang Hang-jun and J.Y. Park!
A world-renowned Korean cinematic legend,
-Chang Hang-jun.
-Sure.
JYP
is here!
THE TWO LEGENDS MEET
He's the happiest filmmaker right now.
It kind of feels like
a huge act of collective mockery.
He had a favor to ask you.
I, J.Y. Park, am a good actor.
I'm built for comedy.
Who could you have played
in The King's Warden?
Yoo Hai-jin's role.
J.Y. Park:
"I can act as well as Yoo Hai-jin."
THE LEGENDS GO BACK AND FORTH
THE FOODIES OF THE SHOW
WILL COOK FOR HANG-JUN
That's one too many tomatoes.
He's cooking his portion too.
Is that for one person?
MOUTH-WATERING VISUALS
That smells so good!
CHINESE VS. WESTERN CUISINE
A CLASH OF PRIDE
We'll take down those lousy Western chefs.
We'll beat the Chinese nobodies.
FIERCE MIND GAMES
Give them a good beating!
WHAT WAS THAT?
THE LUNACY OF THE CHINESE SISTER CHEFS
CLEANSING WITH SALT
GLANCES
GLANCES THE 2ND TIME
Why are you so cautious?
THE NOVICE LEGEND
STILL FINDS ATTENTION AWKWARD?
Don't be so cautious.
You've surpassed ten million admissions.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn